RUBEN DEN HOLLANDER

Portfolio website: rubendenhollander.com
Tel Aviv | (+972) 54-6442746 | struben@gmail.com







Professional Summary

Multilingual (Dutch/English/Hebrew) web developer and digital marketeer. Strong orientation in computer programming and nearly a decade of experience in managing online marketing campaigns and managing affiliate marketing teams. Great communication and organizational skills.

Ability to analyze, prioritize and work under high work pressure.

Computer & Programming skills

HTML, CSS, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript ES6, ReactJS, SQL, git, GitHub, Bootstrap.

Work Experience

2019 Freelance Full Stack Web Developer, Tel Aviv, Israel.

2019 Coding Bootcamp Teaching Assistant, Le Wagon, Tel Aviv, Israel.

2017 – 2018 Senior affiliate manager, NetBet, Tel Aviv, Israel.

Managing online marketing campaigns.

Responsible for affiliate API integrations, working directly with R&D team.

2013 – 2016 Affiliation team leader, ETBO, Ramat Gan, Israel.

Managing a team of 8 affiliate managers.

Optimizing team performance with 8 figure monthly turnover.

Responsible for providing marketing materials, affiliate payments and

Representing the company at international conventions. Created mock-up for new tracking platform with R&D team. Working directly with Head of Marketing, CTO and CFO.

Graduated management course, led by Dr. Dvora Geller, in 2015.

2009 – 2011 Affiliate manager, 888Holdings, Herzliya, Israel.

Running affiliate campaigns for Dutch market.

2002 – 2004 Co-founder & board member of non-profit cultural organization 'Etcultera', Dordrecht, Netherlands.

Raising subsidy funds from municipal cultural department. Organizing events, like music concerts and Big Rivers festival.

Education

2018 - 2018 Le Wagon full stack programming bootcamp, Tel Aviv, Israel.

2015 - 2015 Certificate for Managerial Development Program, Ramat Gan, Israel.

2008 – 2012 BA Government, Strategy, and Diplomacy. IDC, Herzliya, Israel.

2002 – 2004 BA Communication and Information Science. First and Second Year

University of Utrecht, Utrecht, Netherlands.

1995 – 2002 Johan de Witt-Gymnasium, Dordrecht, Netherlands.

Extracurricular Activities

Army service in IDF (Shlav Bet), Israel.

Ambulance first responder volunteer for Magen David Adom, Jerusalem, Israel.

References available upon request